smarthealthmagazine.org 2016-02-29

# Privacy

**This Privacy Policy describes what information Smart Health Magazine and certain third parties gather, how we collect it, our information sharing practices, how users may change the way their information is collected and more.**

**What we collect:**

**Part 1- ‘ _Personal Information’_**

Personal Information generally means information which might reasonably be used to specifically identify you and may include information such as your name, address, age, credit card details, email and phone number. We collect such personal information when you provide it to us, such as when you:

  * Subscribe to the  **Smart Health Magazine**
  * Purchase software license or a product
  * Sign up for email newsletters
  * Enter a sweepstakes
  * Register for site membership and webinars
  * Participate in surveys
  * Create a profile or
  * Otherwise communicate with us.

Several of the services that we offer require registration as a condition of use. We may also receive personal information about you from other sources and add it to the information you have provided to us.

Please note that Smart Health is not responsible for the information you volunteer about yourself in the discussions in our forums, social media pages, blogs, chat rooms, or other publicly accessible interaction, or information that you choose to make public in your member profile or other areas that allow users to upload or post content. We discourage users from posting personally identifiable information in this fashion, and any personally identifiable information you post to these areas is not covered by this Policy. You can change your publicly available information at any time via your profile page.

We use Email Marketing Software to send email to those who are subscribed to our newsletters etc, but these companies do not onsell or own your information and it is stored securely for use of our mailings only. You are able to unsubscribe at any time.

We will never onsell your personal information to another company.

We hate Junk mail as much as you do and you won’t get random emails from us – only those you have subscribed to and updates on your subscription, update on your orders etc.

We do not store any creditcard details.
